- 你还行吗  - 嗯呢
-You right? -Ally: Yep.
- 好了  - 走哪边
-Alright. -Which way?
往这边走
Down here.
- 你还好吧  - 嗯
-Ally: You right? -Yeah.
- 看到了吗  - 看到了
-can you see? -Oh, yeah.
- 她多大了  - 我不知道
-ally: How old is she? -Brittany: I don't know.
- 你不知道啊  - 嘿  布里特  嘘
-You don't know. -Hey, brit! Brit! Shh.
- 看到了吗 -  嗯嗯
- ok. See it? -Mm-hm.
要不要过去看看
Alright. You wanna go down?
去吧  没事的
you're right.
- 来啊 - 来了
-Come on. -Ally: Yeah, ok.
- 她是不是很美  - 是
- isn't she gorgeous? -Yeah.
太美了
She's beautiful!
你看她五彩斑斓的马鬃  好漂亮啊
Look at these colours in her mane. They're amazing.
老爸  来啊
Dad, come on!
- 你要过去吗  - 不了  你去吧
-Are you gonna come over? -Nah, mate. You go.
- 好柔软呀  - 是啊
-She's so soft. -Yeah.
能带她回家吗
Can we take her home?
车里放不下她呀  宝贝
I don't think she'll fit in the car, love.
别乱摸
put that down.
老爸  你看  独角兽的屎
Dad, look! It's unicorn poo.
真好啊
Beauty!
好啦  该走了  宝贝
Alright, better get going, love.
- 走吧 - 我还没看够
-So... -But I wanna stay.
我知道  我们改天再来吧
Yeah, I know. But we'll come back another day, alright?
好
Ok.
拜拜啦
'bye.
我永远不会忘记你的
I will never forget you.
走吧
Let's go, eh?
- 你看  - 好厉害呀
-Look! -Ally: Oh, that's cool.
好看
Beauty.
- 我扶你起来  - 好
-Here, you want a hand? -Yeah.
- 看着树枝啊  - 好  谢了
-Just watch that branch. -I'm right, thanks.
- 好了  可以吗  - 好
-Ally: Yeah, yeah. You got it? -Yeah.
嘿
hey.
好乖
Hey.  good girl.
Good girl.
好乖  好乖
Yeah, good girl, good girl.
我把角拿下来哦
Try and get this horn off, eh?
嘿
- -hey?
好了  好了
There you go. There you go.
我靠
fuck.
- 嘿你好吗  - 能去外面谈一下吗
-how you going? -Can we have a word outside?
好
Sure.
怎么了
what's up?
布里特说你给她性教育谈话了
Brit said you had the sex talk with her.
是啊
Yep.
我没办法控制你说什么不说什么
Look, I'm not having a go at you,
但你不觉得如果你要跟她聊这种事情
but don't you think it's important that
也应该先问问我的意见吗
if you're gonna have those kind of conversations with her,
这很重要啊
you at least flag it with me first?
我没法问你的意见啊
Well, I couldn't flag it with you
她看到我们做爱了
'cause she caught us having sex.
你们是在哪里做的
Where were you having sex?
- 这重要吗  - 没  就是
-Does it matter? -No, just...
怎么  你以为我们就当她面做吗
What, you think we're having sex in front of her or something?
没  我就是
-No, I just... It's just... -
嘿
brittany: Hi.
- 你好呀  - 我们去打保龄球吗
-Hello! -Are we going bowling?
能去打保龄球吗  我不知道啊
"are we going bowling?" uh, I don't know.
我不知道能不能带你去打保龄球呢
I don't know if I'm allowed to take you bowling.
- 问问妈妈吧  - 妈妈  能去打保龄球吗
-You better ask your mum. -Mum, can we go bowling?
当然可以了  宝贝
Course you can go bowling, sweetie.
- 好  - 好
-Cool. -Awesome.
厉害
nice, nice!
打偏了
Brittany: Oh, no!
都打偏了
It's all gone pear-shaped.
- 我还是会赢的  - 不会的
-I'm gonna win still! -No, you're not.
- 就会的  - 我要打爆你了
-Yes, I am! -Nah, I'm gonna kill you now.
- 才不  我会赢的  - 我要好好打了
-No, I'm gonna win. -No, I'm gonna focus now.
哎呀
No!
现在你都有40分了
Now you have...40 points?!
40分了  我追上你了哦
40! I'm catching up.
我早上花了一个小时
I spent an hour this morning going from place to place
到处找正常的早餐吃
just trying to find a normal breakfast.
怎么大家都不吃烤土司培根鸡蛋了吗
What happened to bacon and eggs on toast?
现在全是什么牛油果泥  蛋卷鹌鹑蛋
Now it's all fuckin' smashed avo on a brioche of quail eggs
服务员都是什么叫特里斯坦的
served up by some bloody weekend pilates instructor
周末还教人普拉提的娘炮
man-bun poonce named tristan
还一直跟你说要吃无谷蛋白哦
who wants to give you a lecture about fuckin' gluten-free.
最后我都放弃了
I gave up in the end.
你现在是住在邦代了吗
Are you living in bondi now, eh?
没  我就是带麦迪来沙滩上玩的  我现在住马鲁布拉
No, I just brought maddy over to the beach. I'm in maroubra.
自己吗
On your own?
嗯  我跟佐伊分开了
Me and zoe split up.
什么时候的事啊
When did this happen?
三月初吧
Early March.
谢谢你告诉我啊
Thanks for telling me.
你不会想听这种事的  兄弟
You don't wanna hear about that shit, mate.
那你上班吗
So, you working?
怎么会
How come?
我要干什么啊
What am I gonna do?
总得干点什么啊
You gotta do something, mate.
我能喝饮料吗  老爸
Can I have a drink, dad?
好的  你要什么
Sure, mads. What do you want?
- 柠檬汁  - 柠檬汁啊
-Lemonade. -Lemonade?
那你要说什么
What do you say?
求你啦
Please?
说  求你啦老爸  因为你是世界上最棒的老爸啦
"please, dad, 'cause you are the best dad in the universe"?
求你啦老爸  因为你是世界上最棒的老爸啦
Please, dad, because you are the best dad in the universe.
训练的不错啊  很棒
Well trained. Well done. Mmm.
布里特妮  那边啊
Brittany! Other way!
- 怎么了  - 什么味啊
-what? -What's that smell?
- 什么什么味  - 烟味啊
-What smell? -The cigarette smell.
不知道啊  邻居抽的吧
Dunno. Must be one of the neighbours.
妈妈说你抽烟的
Mum says you smoke.
对啊  我以前抽
Yeah, I used to smoke.
现在不抽了吗
But not anymore?
对啊
Mm-mm.
那拉钩钩
Pinky swear?
我才不要拉钩呢
I'm not gonna pinky swear.
我就是  你知道吧
Look, I... You know...
我偶尔抽一根
I have one occasionally, alright?
那你为什么骗我
Why did you lie?
因为我不想让你知道我抽烟啊
'cause I don't want you knowing that I smoke.
为什么
Why?
我不想让你觉得抽烟是一件好事  然后有天你自己也开始抽烟
I don't want you thinking it's ok and then one day you start.
才不会  抽烟对身体不好
No way. Smoking's bad for you.
会得癌症的  我又不傻
It gives you cancer. I'm not stupid.
我没说你傻啊
Yeah, well, I didn't say you were stupid.
那我也不想你得癌症啊
Well, I don't want you to get cancer.
我也不想得癌症呢
Well, I don't wanna get cancer either.
那你怎么不戒烟啊
Why don't you stop, then?
因为戒烟很难啊
'cause it's not bloody easy to quit, it's...
上瘾的
..Addictive.
为什么啊
Why?
有种东西叫尼古丁
Well, there's this stuff called nicotine.
一种化学物质  知道吧
That's a chemical, alright?
然后烟里面就有这种
And that's in the cigarettes, right?
所以你抽烟的是时候呢  你就习惯了  摄入这个尼古丁了
So when you smoke it, you get used to getting that nicotine.
当你不抽了吧  你大脑里面的受体
So when you stop, the receptors in your brain
因为得不到尼古丁  就开始各种闹腾
don't get the nicotine anymore and they start screaming out
然后你就很难受很烦
and it makes you go crazy.
那你能为我戒烟吗  求你了
Well, will you stop for me, please?
好吧
Alright.
- 保证吗  - 我
-Promise? -Look...
我保证我会试着戒的
I promise you I'll try to quit, ok?
我不能保证一定能做到
I can't guarantee you 100% that I can do it,
但我会努力的好吗
but I'll try, ok?
那你要非常非常努力哦
Well, you need to try really, really hard.
好  我保证我会非常非常努力戒烟的
Ok. I promise I'll try really hard, ok?
- 好 - 好的
-Ok. -Alright.
开心了吗
Happy now?
- 嗯  - 好
-Yes. -Good.
- 你打扫房间了吗  - 没  圣诞节了啊
-Cleaned your room up? -No. It's christmas.
如果你不打扫房间
You don't clean your room up,
圣诞老人就不会给你礼物的
santa won't give you any presents.
你之前说圣诞老人是假的
You told me santa's not real.
好吧  要是你不打扫你那脏兮兮的房间
Yeah, well, I won't give you any presents
我就不会给你礼物  这样如何
if you don't clean your bloody room - how's that?
- 好吧  - 再见
- fine.   - Mm-hm. Bye-bye.
不是那个
Nah, not that one.
是的
Yeah.
- 那是谁送的  布里特  - 布鲁斯叔叔送的
-  Who's that from, brit?  - From uncle bruce.
好吧
Ah, ok.
酷  谢谢
Oh, cool! Thanks.
不错吧
Is it alright?
是的  很棒
Yeah, it's great.
不客气  小美女
You're welcome, beautiful.
你现在就想要你的礼物吗
Do you want your present now?
- 你给我买礼物了  - 是啊
- You got me a present?  - Mm-hm.
当然
Sure!
- 你准备好了吗  - 是的
- Are you ready? - Yeah.
告诉布鲁斯叔叔  你的礼物是什么  布里特
Tell uncle bruce what your present is, brit.
我给你写了一些笑话
Oh, um, I wrote you some jokes.
- 你写了笑话  - 是啊
- You wrote some jokes?  - Mm-hm.
告诉他  你长大后想干什么
Tell him what you wanna be when you grow up.
喜剧演员
A stand-up comedian.
喜剧演员  哇
A stand-up comedian? Wow!
什么时候的事
When did this happen?
这只是她这周想要的  伙计
Oh, this is just what she wants to be this week, mate.
下周就会变了
It'll change next week.
- 好吧  - 加油  布里特
- Alright.  - Go for it, brit.
什么东西又黑又黏
What's brown and sticky?
我不知道  是什么
I don't know. What?
棍子
A stick.
很棒
Oh!  oh, very good.
为什么小鸡要过马路
Why did the chicken cross the road?
我不知道  为什么小鸡要过马路
I don't know. Why did the chicken cross the road?
是我问你的  你为什么要问我
Why are you asking me? I asked you.
哈
Eh?
别看我  伙计
Don't look at me, mate.
很好
very good.
- 敲  敲  - 是谁啊
- Knock, knock.  - Who's there?
插嘴牛
Interrupting cow.
- 插嘴  - 哞
- Interrup...  - Moo!
你逗到我了  很好
Ohh! You got me. Very good.
很好  精彩
Very good! Bravo.
谢谢你  小美人
Thank you, beautiful.
- 你为我准备了什么  伙计  - 你
- What'd you get me, mate?  - You?
在这
Oh...Here we go.
- 你给我这个  - 是的
- Oh, you got me one of those. - Yeah.
我给你的东西一样  不过我给你两个
Oh, ok. I got you the same thing but I got you two of 'em.
谢谢
Oh, thank you!
- 那是给艾丽的吗  - 是的
- Is that for ally?  - Yeah.
你要给她什么
Yeah? What did you get her?
我给她做了条项链
I made her a necklace.
- 你做的  - 是的
- You made it? - Yeah.
她会喜欢的
She'll love that!
好了  所有东西都拿了吧
Alright. Got all your stuff?
伙计  你确定你不想去吗
Alright, mate. Sure you don't wanna come?
嗯  不去了
Nah, mate, I'm good.
- 你准备做什么  - 我要放松下
- What are you gonna do? - I'm gonna take it easy.
- 好吧  快来  小家伙  - 再见
- Alright. Come on, buggerlugs. - 'bye!
你看着很漂亮
You look beautiful!
- 谢谢  - 谢谢  伙计
- Thanks.  - Thanks, mate.
没说你
Not you!
- 圣诞快乐  - 圣诞快乐
-Merry christmas!  - Merry christmas.
圣诞快乐  回头见
Merry christmas, mate. See you in a bit.
好的
Yeah.
32号
32.
想按门铃吗
wanna ring that bell there?
房子很漂亮  对吧
nice house, eh?
圣诞快乐
Hi! Merry christmas!
亲爱的
Hi, darling. Ohh!
没必要那么客气的  谢谢
Oh, you didn't have to do that! Thank you!
进来  快进来
Come in, come in, come in!
- 圣诞快乐  - 圣诞快乐
- Merry christmas.  - Merry christmas.
我们开始吧
So what... Oh, here we go.
- 再问一遍  你妈妈叫什么  - 莎莉
- What's your mum's name again?  - Sally.
- 你好  - 嗨
-Hello! - Hi!
- 圣诞快乐  - 妈  这是布里特妮
- Merry christmas! - Mum, this is brittany.
- 这是雷  - 你好啊
- This is ray.  - How you doing?
- 你好啊  雷  - 给我  等会
- How you doing, ray? - Oh, here, hang on.
- 圣诞快乐  欢迎  - 圣诞快乐
- Merry christmas. Welcome.  - Merry christmas to you too.
- 房子很漂亮  - 非常感谢
- Nice house.  - Oh! Thank you very much.
你要来杯起泡苹果汁吗
Did you want a sparkling apple juice?
- 好的  谢谢  - 要
- Yes, please.  - Yes?
- 我现在能打开这个吗  - 可以
-And can I open this now? -Yes.
- 你要啤酒  还是红酒   - 都可以
- Would you like a beer, wine?  - Yeah, that'd be great, yeah.
- 出来吧  - 好的  酷
- Come on outside.  - Ok. Cool.
我们都在这里吃饭呢
This is where it's all happening.
如果你和一个著名的侦探
So, "what do you get
一起穿过一具骨架  你会得到什么
"if you cross a skeleton with a famous detective?"
得到什么  老爸
What, dad?
夏洛克的骨头
"sherlock bones."
拜托
Oh, come on!
- 我更喜欢香肠  - 给你
- I like the sausage one better.  - Here you go, mum.
- 老爸的笑话很糟糕  - 谢谢  亲爱的
- Dad's jokes are awesome. -Thanks, love.
- 天才  他是个天才  - 太好笑了
- genius. He's a genius.  - That is a cracker.
你还好吗
Are you ok?
我想抽一根烟
I need a smoke.
那就去抽啊
Well, go have one.
不行  我答应过布里特戒烟的
I can't. I promised brit I'd give up.
圣诞节戒烟啊
On christmas day?
天哪
Jesus h.
- 很好  - 嘿  雷
-Ok. Good. - Hey, ray!
你以前有玩过神秘圣诞老人吗
Ever played secret santa before?
老兄
Nah, mate.
老兄  这是你一生中最棒的时刻
Oh, mate, you are in for the time of your life!
我们这有12个人
Ok, the way it works, there's 12 of us in here.
这里有12张小卡片  写着1-12的数字
There's all little cards in here with numbers on. 1-12.
每个人拿一个号码
Everybody takes a number.
来啊  特洛伊  进来拿
Come on, troy! Come on in, mate.
你拿到了一个号码
You grab a number there.
接下来  无论谁拿到了1号
Ok, now, what's gonna happen is that whoever draws number 1,
就得第一个上
they get to go up there first.
- 给你  特洛伊  - 谢谢  老大
- There you go, t-roy.  - Thanks, boss.
2号  跟着他们上
Number 2, they follow them up
也挑一个礼物拿走
and get to pick a present as well.
现在  有意思的来了
Now, here's where it gets interesting.
要是他们不喜欢自己的礼物
If they don't like their present
他们能和1号换
they can swap it with number 1.
也就是说12号是最好的
Which means number 12 is the best place to be, ok?
因为你最后能和所有人换礼物
Because you get to pick from all the other presents at the end.
我的是4号
And here's me - I got number 4.
- 谁是1号  - 又是我
- Who's number 1? - Oh, that's me. Again.
和去年一样
Same as last year!
每年都这样  你个笨笨
Every year! Loser!
老爸
oh, dad!
我能看下这些都是什么吗
Ok. Can I check what they all...All are?
别晃得太厉害  有些是易碎的
Don't shake too hard. Some are breakable.
好了  我要这个藏起来的
alright, I'll go for the hidden one.
- 肯定是鱼缸  - 我猜是本书
- A fishbowl for sure!  - I'm guessing a book.
看看是什么  是
What do we got? We've got...
如何用50种语言侮辱别人
Oh! 'how to insult people in 50 languages'.
- 太有用了  - 对你来说简直完美  亲爱的
- How useful!  - That's perfect for you, love.
你已经知道要怎么做了
You already know how to do that!
让自己
*  have yourself...
光剑
a lightsaber!
过一个快乐的圣诞节
*  a merry little christmas...
你想做什么  你想要换吗
what do you wanna do, zo? Do you wanna swap it?
让你的新变得轻松  - 不  我不想
-*  let your heart be light... *  -no! No, I don't wanna...
不止一个  有两个
Not just one. Two!
从今以后  - 闭上眼睛
-*  from now on... *  -block your eyes!
我们的烦恼就会消失不见
*  our troubles will be out of sight...
- 那个满意吗  - 是的
- happy with that one?  - Yeah.
- 她想要  - 让自己
- she wants it.   -*  have yourself
- 过个快乐的  - 圣诞快乐
-*  a merry little... *  -merry christmas!
圣诞节
*  christmas...
恐龙  恐龙模型
dino... Dino moulds.
看起来很棒
Yeah, that looks great, yeah.
我要和你换下  不好意思
I'm gonna have to swap, I'm sorry.
从现在开始
* from now on...
这个礼物很好啊  不错啊
dad: Oh, that's a beautiful present. Good on you, mate.
最幸运的最后一个  12号是特伦特
Ok, and lucky last, number 12 is trent!
来吧  孩子
Come on up here, son.
来啊
-Come on! -
好像是易碎的
sounds broken.
这个是小心轻放的那个
that's the 'shake gently' one, yeah.
肯定是茶杯  肯定是
I bet you it's teacups. I bet you.
- 你看  我说吧  - 还是一对的
-See? I told you. -Oh, the couple together.
还很像你俩啊  很好啊
See, they even look like the two of you. That's perfect.
谢了  姐姐
Trent: Thanks, sis.
拿着吧  这个给你
Ally: Take these! Go on, you want this.
老爸  这个看着很好啊
Well, dad, those... Those do look good.
他要拿耳机了
Man: He's going for the headphones!
我喜欢盒子里的东西啊
But I think I like what's in the box.
- 才不是  - 特伦特啊
-Oh, you're not! -Woman: Trent!
- 我靠了  - 真的吗
-Come on! -Trent. Really?
- 怎么了  可以交换啊 - 她还是小孩啊
-What? Hey, it's the rules. -She's just a kid.
你拿个独角兽干嘛啊
Man: What are you gonna do with a unicorn?
- 还不知道  - 好啦
-I don't know yet. -Dad: Alright, everybody.
把包装纸收一下
Let's...Let's clean the place up,
把这里打扫一下
pick up all the papers,
然后去外面喝一杯  好不好
then we'll go have a drink outside - what do you say?
圣诞快乐  拿个袋子
Woman: Merry christmas! Grab a bag.
罗比  你在吃你的包装纸吗
Robby, are you chewing yours?
- 怎么了  哥们  - 挺好的
-how's it going, dude? -Yeah, good.
抽烟吗
Smoke?
我戒了
Nah, I gave up.
- 我也该戒烟的  - 是啊
-Yeah, I should. -Yeah, you should.
你还记得那个独角兽蜡烛吧
Hey, you know that... That unicorn candle?
嗯呢  很好看啊
Yeah, it's pretty cool, isn't it?
对啊  你能把它还回来吗
Yeah. Yeah. Is there any chance you can give it back?
为什么
Why?
我女儿
Well, my daughter,
目前很喜欢独角兽啊
she's kind of obsessed with unicorns at the moment.
是啊
-Yeah. -And, uh...
然后我就寻思  你能不能还给她
I was hoping maybe, you know, you'd give it back
然后我
and, you know, I'll...
给你一百澳币什么的
..Throw you a hundred bucks or something.
你是要贿赂我
You trying to bribe me
把独角兽蜡烛给你女儿吗
to give your daughter the unicorn candle?
我没说我要贿赂你
I wouldn't say I'm bribing you.
更像是
More like I'm...
求你帮个忙  对吧
..Asking you a favour, you know?
如果可以的话
And if you can do it,
我就会表示感谢  然后给你一点现金
I'll show a bit of gratitude and throw you some cash.
我看着好像缺那一百块的人吗
Do I look like I need the money?
我没说你看着好像缺钱
I don't think you look like you need the money.
你知道我一年能挣多少钱吗
You know how much I make in a year?
你为啥这么混蛋啊
Why are you being a dickhead?
我觉得咱俩之中有一个人挺混蛋的
yeah, I think one of us is being a dickhead.
你他么为什么要拿走一个小孩的礼物啊
Why the fuck would you take a present off a little kid?
你都这么大个人了
You're a grown man.
你他么拿个小姑娘蜡烛干嘛啊
What the fuck do you want with a fuckin' girly candle?
因为这小玩意挺朦胧的
'cause it's kitschy.
朦胧
It's kitschy?
是啊  朦胧
Yeah. Kitschy.
各位小姑娘小伙子们
* hail the new, ye lads and lasses
我们一起开心快乐
* sing we joyous all together
阳光明媚  风和日丽
* heedless of the wind and weather...
- 小心手  老妈  - 老妈
-ally: Careful, mum. -Trent: Mum!
小心  老爸  去拿个
Careful. Dad, can you get...
老爸  艾丽弟弟怎么了啊
Hey, dad. What happened with ally's brother?
好像绊倒了吧
I think he tripped over.
喝酒喝太多了
He had a bit much to drink.
- 所以他喝醉了啊 - 我觉得是
-So he was drunk? -Yeah, I think so.
- 那你怎么把蜡烛拿回来的
How come you took the candle off him?
他不想要了
Oh, he didn't really want it.
那我要把我的礼物给他吗
Should I give him my present, then?
不用  你留着吧
No, you keep it.
好了  亲一下
Righto, love. Give us a kiss.
么么哒
Mwah!
晚安
G'night.
- 再见啦  - 拜拜
-See ya! -'bye.
- 嘿 - 嘿
-jacinta: Hey! -Hi.
- 怎么样啊 - 很好
-How was it? -Good.
- 玩的开心吗  - 嗯
-Did you have fun? -Yeah.
- 对不起啊  - 嗯
-I'm sorry. - yeah.
我不是要找借口
I'm not making excuses, but...
布里特今天早上抓到我抽烟了
..Brit caught me smoking this morning
她让我保证要戒烟
and, um, she made me promise to give up
我一天没抽烟了
and I hadn't smoked all day and...
你懂吗
You know.
嗯  行
Fair enough.
你没事吧
You're ok?
- 有事  - 嗯
-No. -Yeah.
嗯  行
Fair enough.
你弟弟咋样了
What about your bro?
还好吗
He alright?
你觉得能好吗
How do you think?
你知道之前跟我订婚的那个人吧
So you know that guy that I was engaged to, yeah?
我跟他分手了
I ended that.
我们在一起差不多
We were together for...
三年了
..I don't know, three years.
他有时候跟你一样
He had demons like you.
会发泄  砸东西
He used to lash out and smash things
砸墙
and punch walls.
然后有一天他开始打我了
And then one day he started on me.
他就跟我道歉  然后说爱我
He apologised and told me that he loved me and...
然后我就原谅他
..I forgave him.
然后几周之后
And then a few weeks later, he, um...
他又扇我
..Slapped me.
之后开始踢我  揍我
After that, he kicked me, punched me.
每次  他都会说
And every time, you know, he'd say...
对不起
.."I'm sorry."
然后说他爱我
and told me that he loved me.
所以
So...
而且他也不是坏人
And he's not a bad person.
我之前一直那么告诉自己
I used to tell myself that all the time.
他就是  支离破碎
He's just... He's damaged and...
我以为我能拯救他的
I thought that I could save him.
我努力了
and I tried, I really...
真的很努力
I really tried.
但我没办法
But I couldn't.
你有黑暗的一面
there's a darkness in you.
我觉得可能一开始
And I think that's one of the things
被你吸引也是因为这个
that attracted me to you in the first place.
但现在我觉得
But now I think...
我也不知道
I don't know. I think that...
我觉得我爱你的那些东西  现在开始让我害怕了
..The very thing I loved about you, now it scares me.
我永远不会打你的啊
I'd never hit you.
他之前也是这么说的
That's what he used to say.
我不能再冒这个险了
And I can't take that chance.
就是不能  对不起
-Mmm. -I can't. I'm sorry.
所以  我们就
So that's it?
嗯
Yeah.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我也是
So am I.
我爱你
I love you.
真的  要记住
I do. Know that.
从一个你很爱的人身边离开
And walking away from someone that you love
真的是世界上最他么难的事情了
is one of the hardest fucking things in the world to do.
是啊
Yeah.
那
Well...
好吧
yeah.
好
Alright.
照顾好自己
Look after yourself.
你也是
You too.
我不希望自己再犯错
* I hope that I won't be that wrong anymore
或许我这次得到了教训
* and maybe I've learned this time
我希望我能找到
* I hope that I find
我想要的一切
* what I'm reaching for
我脑海中的一切
* the way that it is in my mind
希望有点我可以放下你
* some day I'll get over you
我会一直等待这一天
* I'll live to see it all through
但我也会永远怀念
* but I'll always miss
梦里梦到你
* dreaming my dreams
和我一起
* with you...